<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Doctor360</string>
    <string name="app_final">DOCTOR360</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>

    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_request">Referred Doctors</string>
    <string name="menu_patient_request">Patient Request</string>
    <string name="menu_chat_room">Chat Room</string>
    <string name="menu_doctors">Doctors List</string>
    <string name="menu_qna">QnA</string>
    <string name="menu_faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="menu_about_us">About Doctor360</string>
    <string name="menu_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="menu_logout">Logout</string>

    <string name="no_account">Not registered to Doctor360 yet?</string>
    <string name="yes_account">Already registered to Doctor360?</string>
    <string name="patient_session">Sign up as Patient</string>
    <string name="doctor_session">Sign up as Doctor</string>
    <string name="session">Sign in to start your session</string>
    <string name="signin">Sign in</string>
    <string name="signup">Sign up</string>
    <string name="signup_as">SIGNUP AS</string>
    <string name="signin_as">SIGN IN</string>
    <string name="signup_patient">As Patient</string>
    <string name="signup_doctor">As Doctor</string>
    <string name="remember_me">Remember Me</string>

    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="mobile">Mobile No</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="dob">Date of Birth</string>
    <string name="age">Age</string>
    <string name="blood_group">Blood Group</string>
    <string name="specialization">Specialization</string>
    <string name="qualification">Qualification</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="old_password">Current Password</string>
    <string name="new_password">New Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_new_password">Confirm New Password</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="document">Document Image (jpeg, jpg or png format)</string>
    <string name="update_profile">Update Profile</string>
    <string name="click_photo">Click Photo</string>
    <string name="upload_photo">Upload Photo</string>

    <string name="version">Version 1.0</string>
    <string name="slogan">Your Health, Our Treatment</string>

    <string name="slide_1_title">Video Consultation</string>
    <string name="slide_1_desc">Online video Consultations with certified doctors</string>

    <string name="slide_2_title">Appointment with Doctor</string>
    <string name="slide_2_desc">Booking Appointment with Specialist</string>

    <string name="slide_3_title">Consult a Doctor</string>
    <string name="slide_3_desc">You can consult a doctor online at your comfort</string>

    <string name="slide_4_title">Search Right Doctor</string>
    <string name="slide_4_desc">Search the right doctor, view doctors details and reviews</string>

    <string name="password_policy">Password Policy</string>
    <string name="policy1">Must have at least 1 special character</string>
    <string name="policy2">Must have at least 1 upper case letter</string>
    <string name="policy3">Must have at least 1 lower case letter</string>
    <string name="policy4">Must have at least 1 digit</string>
    <string name="policy5">Must be equal or more than 8 characters</string>
    <string name="no_internet">No Internet Connection. Please check your connection and try again.</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_change_password">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="action_profile">My Profile</string>
    <string name="action_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="dashboard">Dashboard</string>

    <string name="unverified">Unverified</string>
    <string name="verified">Verified</string>
    <string name="verify">Verify</string>
    <string name="reject">Reject</string>
    <string name="unverified_doctors">Unverified Doctors</string>
    <string name="verified_doctors">Verified Doctors</string>

    <string-array name="genderList">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="bloodList">
        <item>A+</item>
        <item>A-</item>
        <item>B+</item>
        <item>B-</item>
        <item>O+</item>
        <item>O-</item>
        <item>AB+</item>
        <item>AB-</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="qualificationList">
        <item>Bachelor of Medicine (MBBS, BMBS, MBChB, MBBCh)</item>
        <item>Bachelor of Surgery (MBBS, BMBS, MBChB, MBBCh)</item>
        <item>Bachelor of Medicine (B.Med)</item>
        <item>Bachelor of Surgery (B.S)/(B.Surg)</item>
        <item>Doctor of Medicine (MD, Dr.MuD, Dr.Med)</item>
        <item>Doctor of Osteopathic Medicine (DO)</item>
        <item>Doctor of Medicine by research MD(Res), DM</item>
        <item>Master of Clinical Medicine (MCM)</item>
        <item>Master of Medical Science (MMSc, MMedSc)</item>
        <item>Master of Public Health (MPH)</item>
        <item>Master of Medicine (MM, MMed)</item>
        <item>Master of Philosophy (MPhil)</item>
        <item>Master of Philosophy in Ophthalmology (MPhO)</item>
        <item>Master of Public Health and Ophthalmology (MPHO)</item>
        <item>Master of Surgery (MS, MSurg, MChir, MCh, ChM, CM)</item>
        <item>Master of Science in Medicine or Surgery (MSc)</item>
        <item>Doctor of Clinical Medicine (DCM)</item>
        <item>Doctor of Clinical Surgery (DClinSurg)</item>
        <item>Doctor of Medical Science (DMSc, DMedSc)</item>
        <item>Doctor of Surgery (DS, DSurg)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sepcializationList">
        <item>Allergists/Immunologists</item>
        <item>Anesthesiologists</item>
        <item>Cardiologists</item>
        <item>Colon and Rectal Surgeons</item>
        <item>Critical Care Medicine Specialists</item>
        <item>Dermatologists</item>
        <item>Endocrinologists</item>
        <item>Emergency Medicine Specialists</item>
        <item>Family Physicians</item>
        <item>Gastroenterologists</item>
        <item>Geriatric Medicine Specialists</item>
        <item>Hematologists</item>
        <item>Hospice and Palliative Medicine Specialists</item>
        <item>Infectious Disease Specialists</item>
        <item>Internists</item>
        <item>Medical Geneticists</item>
        <item>Nephrologists</item>
        <item>Neurologists</item>
        <item>Obstetricians and Gynecologists</item>
        <item>Oncologists</item>
        <item>Ophthalmologists</item>
        <item>Osteopaths</item>
        <item>Otolaryngologists</item>
        <item>Pathologists</item>
        <item>Pediatricians</item>
        <item>Physiatrists</item>
        <item>Plastic Surgeons</item>
        <item>Podiatrists</item>
        <item>Preventive Medicine Specialists</item>
        <item>Psychiatrists</item>
        <item>Pulmonologists</item>
        <item>Radiologists</item>
        <item>Rheumatologists</item>
        <item>Sleep Medicine Specialists</item>
        <item>Sports Medicine Specialists</item>
        <item>General Surgeons</item>
        <item>Urologists</item>

    </string-array>

    <string name="about">About Doctor360</string>
    <string name="about1">Doctor360 is the First Online Healthcare Service Provider from Nepal where patients can consult certified medical personnel and get additional health related services along with other information related to health online.</string>
    <string name="about2">We understand that getting medical information and health advice from doctors should be easier and technology can bridge this gap between doctors and patients in our country. Hamro doctor is our attempt to change the face of healthcare in our country and make health care less complicated and make it widely and easily accessible.</string>
    <string name="about3">One can get detailed , personalized research based and certified information along with expert opinions from qualified doctors. This service is used commonly in order to understand medical condition, diagnosis, treatment options or alternatives and recommendations for future therapeutic conditions.</string>
    <string name="about4">Doctor360 is also  a virtual community where doctors and patients can engage in live chats and discussions in order to make things more convenient.  Our facilities help patients understand their health better, make better decisions related to their health and find the best doctors and the best cure.</string>
    <string name="about5">Our services not only help doctors get patients but it also improves their overall reputation and also expands their work to a larger audience. Patients can also keep a record of their medical history along with their profiles, saving them from the hassle of carrying medical files and reports here and there.</string>
    <string name="about6">Doctor360 was founded with a vision of making health care and medical consultation less complicated and widely accessible. We aim to develop a trustworthy health care service which is personalized and less sophisticated. Along with online consultation we also provide services like blood donation, online discussion and health feed. </string>

    <string name="faq0_title">1.What is Doctor360?</string>
    <string name="faq0_desc">Doctor30 is an online platform serving patients and doctors by eliminating the boundaries of quality healthcare via online video consultations, managing patient’s self and family medical records with great user experience on mobile devices.</string>

    <string name="faq1_title">2.How can I access Doctor360?</string>
    <string name="faq1_desc">Doctor360 can be access via android app. Our iOS app is being released soon.</string>

    <string name="faq2_title">3.Is the any charges to use Doctor360?</string>
    <string name="faq2_desc">No. There is no any charges to use this app. Its free for all users.</string>

    <string name="faq3_title">4.What I can ask to doctor?</string>
    <string name="faq3_desc">Any medical question that you need to ask with a doctor who specializes in that area. Our doctors help with pregnancies, fevers, colds, sexual issues, weight and a whole lot more.</string>

    <string name="faq4_title">5.Is Doctor360 app safe to use?</string>
    <string name="faq4_desc">Yes. We have a team of carefully selected and personally verified MD and MBBS doctors from across Nepal. Each doctor has received extensive training to consult you over the app. </string>

    <string name="faq5_title">6.Why do Doctor360 ask for personal details?</string>
    <string name="faq5_desc">We need your mobile number, email to ensure that you can be immediately informed when your doctor responds or when your medicines ship or to schedule your tests.</string>

    <string name="faq6_title">7.Do you have specialists (Gynecologists, Psychologists, etc.)?</string>
    <string name="faq6_desc">Yes, we strive hard to ensure that you get to discuss your concern with a MD or MS who specializes in that area. </string>

    <string name="faq7_title">8.What are the services timings?</string>
    <string name="faq7_desc">Our doctors are available 24/7. Only our specialty doctors are subjected to availability during late hours (11PM to 6:00AM). However, all times you can contact our support team under support chat section if you need further assistance.</string>

    <string name="faq8_title">9.Will my chat with the doctor remain private?</string>
    <string name="faq8_desc">Doctor360 is a safe and secure online consultation application. We have made sure that the user data, medical records and information, and the chats are end-to-end encrypted to give users the privacy needed to use the application.</string>

    <string name="faq9_title">10.Can I choose any doctor?</string>
    <string name="faq9_desc">Yes. You can choose your doctor from the list provided in the Doctor360 application.</string>

    <string name="faq10_title">11.Can I use other user account to see a doctor?</string>
    <string name="faq10_desc">No, you will be provided a dedicated account to get in touch with doctors. Using another user account will confuse the doctors as it will not match the medical records and information available in the user profile.</string>

    <string name="faq11_title">12.How can Doctor360 help to grow a doctor medical practices?</string>
    <string name="faq11_desc">Doctor360 acts as a platform for doctors to take up online consultation and expand their medical practice into an online platform. Doctors can offer video and audio consultation with the help of appointments scheduled by the patients.</string>

    <string name="faq12_title">13.How can I book an online consultation with a doctor and appointment before visiting a hospital?</string>
    <string name="faq12_desc">The online consultation and appointment can be booked by going through the Consultation and Appointment option respectively on the Doctor360 Application</string>

    <string name="faq13_title">14.I am outside Nepal. How can I book an online consultation?</string>
    <string name="faq13_desc">That is not a problem at all. You can still book an online consultation with the doctors regarding the problem on the Doctor360 app.</string>

    <string name="faq14_title">15.Can I use Doctor360 on multiple devices?</string>
    <string name="faq14_desc">No, a user will only be able to log in through Android app at a time for now. We are going to release iOS soon.</string>

    <string name="faq15_title">16.I do not know which specialty I should choose for my problem?</string>
    <string name="faq15_desc">If you are not aware of which specialty to post your query in, the moderation team will divert your query to the right doctor.</string>

    <string name="faq16_title">17.Will my phone number be revealed during a phone consultation?</string>
    <string name="faq16_desc">During a phone consultation, neither the doctor nor the user will be able to give the personal contact details of the other party. The call will be connected through an anonymous calling system.</string>

    <string name="faq17_title">18.How do I share this service with a friend?</string>
    <string name="faq17_desc">vYou can provide a promotional code to your friend, who is not already registered on the site. If the new user registers using this specific promo code, referral bonuses will be added to both of your wallets.</string>

    <string name="faq18_title">19.How do I search for a doctor?</string>
    <string name="faq18_desc">You can search for a specific doctor registered on Doctor360 in the Doctors page. This page will also provide you the option to filter doctors based on your requirements.</string>

    <string name="faq19_title">20.Are my personal details secure?</string>
    <string name="faq19_desc">All personal details you enter in your query are secure.</string>

    <string name="faq20_title">21.How long will it take for a doctor to answer my queries?</string>
    <string name="faq20_desc">Typically, the doctor will answer as soon as they see the query. It takes around 4 to 8 hours on an average. The deadline for free queries is 24 hours, common or direct queries is 4 to 8 hours, and that of priority fast track queries is 1 hour.</string>

    <string name="privacy_title">1. Introduction to Privacy Practices For Doctor360</string>
    <string name="privacy1">Doctor360 is committed to respecting the privacy rights of all users of Doctor360 services provided via Doctor360 and to protecting your personal and medical information. This policy describes how information about you may be used, how it may be disclosed and how you may access this information.</string>
    <string name="privacy2">This page will serve as a policy of our privacy practices and a summary of your privacy rights.</string>
    <string name="privacy3">We created this Site Privacy Policy to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy.This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site or any website of Doctor360’s partners, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. Your use of the Site is governed by this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. If you are registering an account or using the Site on behalf of an individual or entity other than yourself, you represent that you are authorized by such individual or entity to accept this Privacy Policy on such individual or entity behalf.</string>
    <string name="privacy4">Please note our primary concern is to provide a platform for quick and simple online consultation.</string>
    <string name="privacy5">Be advised, in case your medical question or consultation contains matters of high security risk or there is a high privacy concern (like matter of Federal or State importance, matters related to judiciary, matters related to police or law enforcement) we suggest you to use alternate services or to use face to face medical consultations.It is advisable to include only relevant de-identifiable Personal Information in medical history and files uploaded by you.</string>
    <string name="privacy6">If you do not agree to terms of our Privacy Policy we kindly request you to not use this app.</string>

    <string name="privacy_title1">2. Information that may be collected</string>
    <string name="privacy7">In order to use Doctor360, you are asked to enter an email address and password, which we refer to as your User ID. After you create your ID, you can use the same ID to sign in to this service. This process will allow you to manage your profile and/or account; upload files (medical scans and documents) and ask specific queries.</string>
    <string name="privacy8">When asking questions, you will be asked to submit personal information like date of birth, gender, height, weight, blood group etc. Providing us with other personal and identifiable information is, of course, optional and not highly recommended.</string>
    <string name="privacy9">However, in some cases it may not be possible for us to provide the service in question without receiving specific medical information from you and in some cases you would be requested by the consulting Physician to provide additional information in order to answer your questions. Additional information could be details of your medical history, specific medical reports, etc.</string>
    <string name="privacy10">We automatically track and collect domain servers, type of os, os version and domain servers used to access the app, referring source to the app and your interaction with the app and the os version.We also collect information you provide voluntarily in free-form text boxes on the Site and through responses to surveys, questionnaires and the like.</string>

    <string name="privacy_title3">3. Application Analytics</string>
    <string name="privacy11">We may use third party website analytics services in connection with the app. These app analytics services do not collect Personal Information that you do not voluntarily enter into the app. These services do not track your app habits across apps which do not use their services. We are using the information collected from these services to find usability problems to make the app easier to use.</string>
    <string name="privacy12">The recordings will never identify you or your account.</string>

    <string name="privacy_title4">4. How information about you may be used by Doctor360</string>
    <string name="privacy13">Personal information like your medical history (optional), gender and age details is collected when you start a new consultation request. These are saved in your account for future reference and future consultation requests.</string>
    <string name="privacy14">These details in conjunction with your questions are shared with Consulting Physicians to help them answer your questions to the best of their knowledge.</string>
    <string name="privacy15">We have a no-spam policy. However, in other instances, non-personal information collected may be used for statistical analysis, improvement of services, and customization of web design, content layout and services.</string>

    <string name="privacy_title5">5. Other Uses of Medical Information</string>
    <string name="privacy16">Other uses and disclosures of medical information not covered by this Notice, or by other laws that apply to us, will be made only with your written permission. If you give your permission to use or share your medical information, you may cancel that permission, in writing, at any time. If you cancel your permission, we will no longer use or share your medical information for the reasons covered in your written permission. We cannot reverse any disclosures we have already made with your permission.</string>

    <string name="privacy_title6">6. Sharing of information</string>
    <string name="privacy17">We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. We do not share your information with third parties for purposes other than that of providing you the services as mentioned in point 8 in this Privacy Policy document.</string>
    <string name="privacy18">You choose whom you want to disclose your personal information to  and how long you want to disclose it.You can even choose how long your information can be shown to your doctor. You can set a certain time limit for your information that is shown to the doctor. After the selected period of time, the doctor will not be able to gain access to your information.</string>
    <string name="privacy19">We strictly do not share any private information regarding our patients to any other party. The information that you provide will be limited to you and your doctor and no one else.</string>

    <string name="privacy_title7">7. User Choice and controlling your Personal Information</string>
    <string name="privacy20">You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you can still access and use much of the Site; however you will not be able to access and use those portions of the Site that require your Personal Information.</string>
    <string name="privacy21">You may choose not to share any medical history with your consultation request. But in the event of the consulting Physician requests you to share more medical information to answer your questions, it is advisable to do so. It is advisable to include only relevant de-identifiable Personal Information in medical history and files uploaded by you.</string>

    <string name="privacy_title8">8. Security</string>
    <string name="privacy22">You make the choice of making your data available to consulting doctors. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information. For example we use firewall security and different degree of encryption for your sensitive personal information.</string>
    <string name="privacy23">Our employees and consulting physicians may share medical information with each other for treatment, payment and operational purposes, only in order to provide efficient healthcare services. We encourage users not to share non-medical identifiable information other than their email and at times a made-up username for public forums.</string>
    <string name="privacy24">We will share your medical information when required to comply with court order or other legal process. We may use and share your medical information to protect the rights, property or safety of Doctor360 or another party, or to respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-parties.</string>
    <string name="privacy25">Although we make good faith efforts to receive, transmit and store Personal Information in a secure operating environment that is not open to the public, you should understand that there is no such thing as complete security, and we do not guarantee that there will be no unintended disclosures of your Personal Information. If we become aware that your Personal Information has been disclosed in a manner not in accordance with this Privacy Policy, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you of the nature and extent of the disclosure (to the extent we know that information) as soon as reasonably possible and as permitted by law.</string>

    <string name="privacy_title9">9. Doctors</string>
    <string name="privacy26">Doctors and their employees should be particularly aware of their obligations of patient confidentiality, both in communicating with Doctor360 and in consulting users via the site. Doctor360 does not have, and will not accept, any obligations of confidentiality with respect to any communications other than those expressly stated in this Privacy Policy and Doctor360 Terms of Use.</string>

    <string name="privacy_title10">10. Public Information</string>
    <string name="privacy27">Any information that you may reveal in a review posting or other online discussion or free forum is intentionally open to the public and is not in any way private. You should think carefully before disclosing any personally identifiable information in any public forum. What you have written may be seen and/or collected by third parties and may be used by others in ways we are unable to control or predict.</string>

    <string name="privacy_title11">11. Updates and Changes to this Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy28">Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Doctor360 is constantly evolving to meet these demands. We therefore reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes).</string>

    <string name="privacy_title12">12. Contact</string>
    <string name="privacy29">If you have comments, concerns or any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@doctor360.com.</string>
    <string name="privacy30">If you do not agree to terms of our Privacy Policy we kindly request you to not use this app.</string>
</resources>
